BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7)
1961- 1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/007
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
These are agreements obtained in the July 1, 1965 surveys in the building trades, printing trades, local trucking, and local transit industries.
5833618
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 09, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Collective labor agreements - United States.; United States. Department of Labor. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
5833618
- Asbestos Workers; Boilermakers; bricklayers; Carpenters; Cement Finishers; Electricians (Inside Wiremen). 1961-1967 (Box 1)
  - Asbestos Workers, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    June 1 1965- May 31 1967
  - Boiler Makers, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    October 1 1963- September 30 1965
  - Boiler makers, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    28 Articles of Agreement booklets
  - Boiler Makers, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    27 Articles of Agreement Booklets
  - Brick Layers, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    One 1964-1966 Agreement booklet
  - Brick Layers, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    2 Agreement booklets also
  - Brick Layers, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    3 Agreement booklets also
  - Carpenters, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    8 Agreement Booklets
  - Carpenters, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    5 'Workers' booklets also
  - Carpenters, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    3 Labor Agreement booklets also
  - Cement Finishers, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cement Finishers, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    5 Workers booklets
  - Cement Finishers, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cement Finishers, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    12 Workers booklets
  - Electricians (Inside Wiremen), 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Electricians (Inside Wiremen), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    6 labor booklets
- Electricians (Inside Wiremen); Engineers; Elevator Constructors; Glaziers; Lathers; Machinists; Marble Setters; Mosaic and Terrazzo Workers; Painters. 1962-1968 (Box 2)
  - Electricians (Inside Wiremen), 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Engineers, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    15 labor Agreement Booklets
  - Engineers, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Engineers, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    21 labor Agreement booklets
  - Engineers, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    10 labor Agreement booklets
  - Elevator Constructors, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    23 Standard Agreement Booklets
  - Glaziers, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Glaziers, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    4 Articles of Agreement Booklets
  - Glaziers, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lathers, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lathers, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lathers, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lathers, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Machinists, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Marble Setters, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mosaic and Terrazzo Workers, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Painters, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    2 Agreement booklets
  - Painters, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Painters, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Pipefitters; Plasterers; Plumbers; Rodmen; Roofers; Sheet Metal Workers; Structural-Iron Workers. 1962-1968 (Box 3)
  - Pipe Fitters, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    11 Agreement Booklets
  - Pipe Fitters, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    4 Agreement booklets
  - Plasterers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Plasterers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Plasterers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Plumbers, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    With collective bargaining agreements
  - Plumbers, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    5 Agreement booklets
  - Plumbers, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    4 Labor Agreement booklets
  - Plumbers, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Various labor agreement pamphlets/booklets
  - Rodmen, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Roofers, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    5 Working agreement Booklets
  - Roofers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    With Agreement booklets
  - Roofers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    6 Agreement booklets
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Various worker agreement booklets
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Stone Masons, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Structural-Iron Workers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    5 Agreement Booklets
- Structural-Iron Workers; Tile Layers; Bricklayers' Tenders; Building Laborers; Marble Setters' Helpers; Plasterers' Laborers; Plumbers' Laborers; Terrazzo Workers' Helpers; Tile Layers' Helpers; Local Transit; Lithographers. 1962-1967 (Box 4)
  - Structural Iron Workers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Structural Iron Workers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    6 Agreement Booklets
  - Tile Layers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tile Layers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bricklayers' Tenders, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Building Laborers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Building Laborers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Building Laborers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    6 Workers Agreement Booklets
  - Marble Setters' Helpers, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Plasterers' laborers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Plumbers' Laborers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Terrazzo Workers' Helpers, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Tile Layers' Helpers, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local Transit, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Multiple Workers' Agreements texts and booklets
  - Local Transit, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    7 Workers' Agreement Booklets
  - Local transit, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    5 Workers' Agreement Booklets
  - Local Transit, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    7 Workers' Agreement booklets
  - Lithographers, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Lithographers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Lithographers; Bookbinders; Compositors; Electrotypers and Stereotypers; Electrotypers; Mailers; Photoengravers: (B&J). 1963-1967 (Box 5)
  - Lithographers, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Lithographers, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lithographers, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Contains some large Agreement Books
  - Lithographers, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    10 Workers Agreement booklets
  - Book Binders (B and J), 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    8 booklets
  - Bookbinders (B and J), 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    9 Booklets
  - Bookbinders (B and J), 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Compositors (B and J), 1962-1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Compositors (B and J), 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    19 Booklets
  - Compositors (B and J), 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    11 Booklets
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Electrotypers (B and J), 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Electrotypers (B and J), 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Millers (B and J), 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Mailers (B and J), 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - photoengravers (B and J), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Photoengravers (B and J), 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Photoengravers (B&J); Pressmen (B&J); Compositors, News; Mailers, News; Photoengravers, News; Pressmen, News. 1963-1968 (Box 6)
  - Photoengravers (B and J), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Photoengravers (B and J), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Pressmen (B and J), 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    5 Workers' agreement booklet
  - Pressmen (B and J), 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Pressmen (B and J), 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    8 Agreement booklets
  - Pressmen (B and J), 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Compositors, News, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    15 Agreement Booklets
  - Compositors, News, 1962-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    7 Agreement Booklets
  - Mailers, News, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mailers, News, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    5 Booklets
  - Mailer, News, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Photoengravers, News, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Photoengravers, News, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Pressmen, News, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Pressmen, News, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    6 Workers Booklets
  - Pressmen, News, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Stereotypers, News; Atlanta, GA; Baltimore, MD; Birmingham, AL; Boston, MA; Buffalo, NY; Charlotte, NC; Chicago, IL; Cleveland, OH; Columbus, OH; Dallas, TX; Dayton, OH; Denver, CO; Detroit, MI; Des Moines, IO; Evansville, IN; Fresno, CA; Grand Rapids, MI (Box 7)
  - Stereotypers, News, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Stereotypers, News, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stereotypers, news, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Atlanta, GA, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Birmingham, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Boston, Mass., 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Charlotte, NC, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chicago, Ill., 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland, Ohio, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Columbus, Ohio, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Dallas, Texas, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dayton, Ohio, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Denver, Colorado, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Detroit, Michigan, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Detroit, Michigan, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Detroit, Michigan, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Des Moines, Iowa, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Evansville, Indiana, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Fresno, California, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Houston, TX; Indianapolis, IN; Jackson, MS; Jacksonville, FL; Kansas City, MO; Knoxville, TN; Little Rock, AR; Louisville, KY; Los Angeles, CA; Madison, WI; Memphis, TN; Milwaukee, WI; Minneapolis-St. Paul, MN; New Haven, CT; New Orleans, LA; New York, NY (Box 8)
  - Houston, Texas, 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Mississippi, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Jacksonville, Florida, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Kansas City, Missouri, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Knoxville, Tennessee, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Louisville, Kentucky, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles, California, 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Madison, Wisconsin (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Memphis, Tennessee, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - New Haven, Connecticut, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - New Orleans, LA, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - New York, NY, 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Norfolk, VA, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Omaha, NB; Peoria, IL; Philadelphia, PA; Phoenix, AZ; Pittsburgh, PA; Portland, OR; Providence, RI; Richmond, VA; Sacramento, CA; St, Louis, MO; Salt Lake City, UT; San Antonio, TX; San Diego, CA; Seattle, WA; San Francisco-Oakland, CA; Shreveport, LA; So (Box 9)
  - Omaha, Nebraska, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Peoria, Illinois, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Phoenix, Arizona, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Portland, Oregon, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Providence, RI, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Richmond, VA, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sacramento, California, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - St. Louis, Missouri, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - San Antonio, Texas, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - San Diego, California, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Seattle, Washington, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - San Francisco, Oakland, California, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - San Francisco/Oakland, California, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - San Francisco/Oakland, California, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Shreveport, LA, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - South Bend, Indiana, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Springfield, Massachusetts, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tampa, Florida, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Topeka, Kansas, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Toledo, Ohio, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Trenton, NJ, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 24)